Jack R. Levien papers MSS15241 MSS 15241
Albert and Shirley Small Special Collections Library
Jack R. Levien papers
1960-1999
Albert and Shirley Small Special Collections Library
MSS 15241
0.8 Cubic Feet 2 document boxes
Book design.; Miniature books.; drawings (visual works); letters (correspondence); photographs; Levien, Jack R.
- Advertisements for J.R. Levien, 1970, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Articles concerning Miniature Books, 1963-1985, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Artwork, Designs and Illustrations for Multiple or Unidentified Works, 1970-1972, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Bibliography of the Books of Jack R. Levien, 1974-1994, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Catalogs featuring Miniature Books, 1970-1983, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Checklists and Notes on Miniature Books, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1960, 1970-1995, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Correspondence concerning Bloem Hofje, 1971, 1980, 1999, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
- News clippings, 1967-1976, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Notecards concerning Miniature Books, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Photographs, chiefly of Miniature Books, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Publications featuring Miniature Books, 1977, 1979, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Typeface Examples, 1970, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Bible Pictures, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Book of Doom, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Business Worries, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- A Child's Bible, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- De Aetna by Pietro Bembo - Notes, etc., 1967, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Decisions, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- "A Dutch Dolls' House" Typescript, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Elizabeth Barrett Browning, [1972] (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Enkhuizen, [1971] (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Have a Cigarette, [1970], [1972] (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Hope, [1972] (Box 2, Folder 11)
- How to Get Out of the Hospital, [1971] (Box 2, Folder 12)
- L'Evangile S. Jean includes a printing plate, [1971] (Box 2, Folder 13)
- "Miniature Book Publishers Directory 1970" (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Nativity Story, [1971] (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Noah's Ark, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Strange Fish, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Selling Primer, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Tower of Babel, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Tribute to Sig, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 20)